amen amen
amen
um I'm going to take this first minute
just to uh encourage you all to start
hitting that share uh
button um if you're inviting people to
come and check this message out now
would be a good time to do it we're just
going to call this the share minute all
right um put a one in the chat y'all if
you are if you're ready for this word
put a one in the chat if you're ready
for this word and uh I I shared with you
a little bit earlier uh that this
message is going to be it's going to be
lifechanging and so I am I'm very
excited um I'm putting a whole bunch of
ones in the chat y'all uh but we're
going to pray and we're going to jump
into this and I'm going to need you to
follow this message really really really
carefully let's do that now Heavenly
Father we come before you at this time
asking that you would please speak to
your
people Lord open our
eyes help us to
see and then Lord help us to
Rejoice this is our prayer in Jesus name
we ask it amen and
amen we're going to go to the screen the
title of the
message is this same
Jesus this
same Jesus in the book of
Acts chapter 1 verse 9 the Bible says
and when he had spoken these things
while they beheld he was taken up and a
cloud received him out of their sight
and while they looked steadfastly toward
the he toward Wards uh while they looked
steadfastly toward Heaven as he went up
behold two men stood by him in white
apparel
and where are
you
wow I I will go ahead and read verse 11
isn't there and it is the
main let me see here I just want to make
sure that it is not here all
right I'll read it with emphasis so you
could hear it
um verse
11 verse 10 and while they stood they
looked steadfastly toward Heaven as he
went up behold two men stood by them in
white apparel which said unto them ye
men of
gallilee why stand ye gazing up into
heaven this same Jesus which is taken up
from you into heaven shall so come in
like manner as you have seen him go into
heaven all right let's come
back uh I was really looking forward to
that uh that verse 11 I don't know how
it got how it got missed but you can see
on the title you can see on the screen
this same Jesus this same
Jesus what a beautiful
thought this same
Jesus that left
is coming again that's what the Angels
were telling the disciples as he ascends
into heaven they're like why are you
gazing this same Jesus is is is the
Jesus that's coming back again and we
know that he's coming back again because
he's coming back to take a people into
heaven put a one in the chat if you are
rejoicing that this same Jesus that left
is coming back to take a people to
Heaven put a one in in the chat if if if
that is if that is good news to you
now in the book of Hebrews Hebrews
chapter 3 we are also given a warning in
Hebrews 3 the Bible says while it is
said today if you will hear his voice
Harden not your hearts as in the
provocation for some when they had heard
did provoke how be it not all that came
out of Egypt by Moses but with whom was
he grieved 40 years was it not them that
had sinned whose carcasses fell in the
wilderness so we see then that they
could not enter in because of unbelief
now uh uh Paul here is is speaking about
the Journey of the children of Israel
from Egypt into the promised land and
what he's saying is because of unbelief
many of those that that were on this
journey did not enter into the promised
land now I'm going to ask you a very
genuine question I want you to to to put
put a three in the chat if that makes
you a little bit nervous because what
Paul is saying here is look just as they
were on a journey into the promised land
so we are on a journey to the promised
land and and and in this journey to the
promised land um
we
are we are in the same danger
of missing out in that
promise missing out in that promise land
now put a three in the chat if that
makes you a little bit
nervous yes yes that that that is caused
for us to be a little bit nervous we
know
that a whole generation did not make it
into the promised land now I need you to
understand that before Jesus
returns there is going to be a
judgment and we speak about this
judgment in fact if we go back to the
screen in Daniel chapter 8 and verse 14
the Bible says he said unto me unto
2,300 days then shall the sanctuary be
cleansed
as as students of Bible prophecy we
understand that this verse is the
cleansing of the sanctuary is a
reference to the day of atonement which
points to a judgment period before Jesus
returns and the Book of Revelation
chapter 14 lets us know uh that this
message is
connected with an end time with the end
time message of of the Three Angels so
the Bible says in Revelation
14:6 it says I saw another angel fly in
the midst of Heaven having the
Everlasting gospel to preach unto them
that dwell on the earth and to every
nation and Kindred and tongue and people
saying with a loud voice fear God and
give glory to him for the hour of his
judgment is come and worship him that
made Heaven the Earth the sea and The
Fountains of waters so the Bible here is
letting us know that just before the
second coming of Christ there is going
to be a judgment there is going to be a
judgment now I'm gonna ask once again uh
if the Judgment makes you a little bit
nervous go ahead a and put that put it
put that three in the chat again if the
Judgment makes you a little bit nervous
go ahead and put that three in the chat
because we know that just as there were
those in the time of is Israel who did
not make it into the promised land H H
so at the end of time there will be
those who do not make it into the
Heavenly Promised
Land There is a judgment that will
determine who enters in and who does
not
now if I tell you you have a court court
case you're going to get nervous court
case man things could go good or they
could go
bad there's a court case every last one
of us has a court
case
and what we're going to do in this
message today is we are actually going
to going to learn about this court case
about this trial but in a way you may
not have heard before
so
um let's go ahead and look up 2 Timothy
chapter 2 verse vers 8 2 Timothy chap
2:8 the Bible says here it says
henceforth there is laid up for me a
crown of righteousness which the Lord
the righteous judge shall give me at
that day and not to me only but unto all
them that also love his appearing all
right so here we see that the judge in
this case is the Lord Jesus Christ put a
five in the chat if you follow that so
far the judge in this court case is the
Lord Jesus
Christ that's good news you
guys the same
Jesus that left this Earth the same
Jesus that is returning is the same
Jesus that is going to be the judge in
this
case
this same
Jesus let's go back to the screen just a
few more verses about judgment the Bible
says in 2 Timothy 4:1 I charge thee
before God and the Lord Jesus Christ who
shall judge the quick and the dead at
his appearing and his kingdom so this
this same Jesus is judging we're told I
saw in Revelation 1911 and I and I saw
uh Heaven opened and behold a white
horse he that sat upon him was called
faithful and true and in righteousness
he doth judge and make war his eyes were
a flame of fire and on his head were
many crowns and he had a name written
which no man knew but himself and he was
clothed with a vesture dipped in Blood
and his name is called the word of God
so what we see here so far is that Jesus
is the one who will be the judge in this
case now I want to talk about the work
of the judge the work of the judge in
Ecclesiastes 12 verse 13 the Bible says
let us hear the conclusion of the whole
matter fear God and keep his
Commandments for this is the whole duty
of man for God shall bring every work
into judgment let's pause for no no no
let's keep reading with every secret
thing whether it be good or whether it
be evil now come back with me for come
back
to the screen for for a
moment the judge is going to bring every
work into
judgment with every secret thing whether
it be good or whether it be
evil did y'all catch
that
everything that we have ever done
everything that that we have ever
thought is going to be considered in
this judgment how many of you are a
little bit more nervous now than you
were at the beginning of this
sermon put a five in the chat if you're
a little bit more nervous now than you
were at the beginning every thought
every
action the Bible say says again in
Romans chap 2:16 in the day when God
shall judge the secrets of men the
secrets of men by Jesus Christ according
to my gospel the work of the judge is to
judge the secrets of
men the work of the judge is to judge
the secrets of men that's what's
happening in this thing that we call the
investigative judgment and now want to
talk to you about the skill of the judge
the skill of the judge notice with me
again uh Psalm 44 verse 21 shall not God
search this out for he knoweth the
secrets of the
heart he knoweth the secrets of the
heart so this tells me that in this case
there is nothing that I have done
that will not be examined there is
nothing that you have done that will not
be examined and now I want you to kind
of grasp if you if you can the
significance of this
judgment couple that with this verse
Romans chapter 3 verse 23 which says for
all have sinned
and come short of the glory of
God all have
sinned all have sinned and come short of
the glory of
God which
means that we are in essence
all
already
guilty are y'all following
this we are are all ready all guilty
because all have sinned and fallen short
of the glory of God so we are already
going into the court case in a bad
way now here comes the good news
y'all the good
news is
that the judge in this case
is this same
Jesus come on let's break it down let's
break it down so if we want to know what
is who is this same Jesus well then it
might be good for us to get to know the
judge in this case right to kind of look
at his life and his character and and
who he is and the kind of things that
this judge does so let's go ahead and
let's just take a let's go back to the
screen and and let's go ahead with uh
let's start with Matthew Matthew chapter
18 verse 14 Matthew chapter 8
ver14 and when Jesus was com into the
house this is the judge right when Jesus
was coming to the into Peter's house he
saw his wife's mother laid and sick of a
fever and he touched her hand and the
fever left left her and she arose and
ministered unto them and when the
evening was come they brought unto him
many that were possessed with devils and
he cast out Spirits with his word and
healed all that were sick that it might
be fulfilled which was spoken by Isaiah
the prophet saying himself took our
infirmities and bear our sicknesses all
right let's pause for a second and a and
and what I want to say to you right
now is that this same
Jesus that healed
that cast out
demons that cared so much about people
that that he he brought them uh life and
health and healing this same Jesus is
the
judge this same Jesus the one you just
read about in that story the guy that
the the man that is like whoa that
that's a nice man to do something like
that same Jesus is the judge
all right let's keep reading how about
this Matthew chapter 8 Matthew chapter 8
verse 23 and behold there arose a great
Tempest in the sea in so much that the
ship was covered with the waves but he
was already but he was asleep and when
he entered into the ship his disciples
followed him and his disciples came to
him and awoke him saying Lord save us we
perish y'all remember that story where
where the disciples are on the boat and
and it seems like the boat is going to
go down and then he saith unto them why
are ye fearful oh ye of little faith
then he arose and rebuked the winds in
the sea and there was a great
calm uhh but the men marveled saying
what manner of man is this that even the
winds and the Sea obey him so remember
this y'all that same
Jesus that same Jesus who cared about
the the fear of the disciples that same
Jesus is the judge in in this
case that same Jesus is the judge in
your
case all right come on let's keep moving
Matthew chapter 8 verse 28 when he was
come to the other side in the country of
the GES or gesses there met him two
possessed with Devils coming out of the
tombs exceeding Fierce so that no man
might P might pass by the weight and
behold they cried out saying what have
we to do with thee Jesus thou Son of God
Art Thou come hither to torment us
before the time and there was a good way
off from them a herd of many swine
feeding so the Devils besought him
saying if thou cast us out suffer us to
go away into the herd of swine and he
said unto them go and when they were
come out they went onto the herd of
swine and behold the whole herd of swine
ran violently down a steep place in the
sea and perished in the waters and in
essence Jesus the Bible says that this
man was now sitting in in his right mind
this same
Jesus that took the time to deliver a
demon-possessed man that same man is the
judge in your
case y'all y'all y'all ought to be
catching some hope right now y'all ought
to be getting a little excited right now
that wait a minute that's the judge you
ever been in a court
and when you go into court you're
waiting to see who the judge is and you
try to read his face and his demeanor
and see like what kind of a man or woman
is this judge do they look like a happy
person do they look like a grumpy person
because if I can figure these things out
I can pretty much know how my case is
gonna
go and imagine Jesus walking in and
sitting down on his throne when the
judgment begins and you're oh that's the
judge all right come on come on let's
keep going let's keep moving Matthew 9:1
and he entered into a ship and passed
over and came into his own City and
behold they brought to him a man sick of
the pausy lying in a bed and Jesus
seeing their faith said unto the sick of
the py son be of good chair thy sins be
forgiven thee and behold certain of the
scribes said within themselves this man
blasphemeth and Jesus knowing their
thoughts said wherefore think ye evil in
your heart s for whether is it easier to
say thy sins be forgiven thee or to say
arise and walk but that you may know
that the son of man has power on Earth
to forgive sins then he says to the sick
of the py arise take up thine bed and go
into thine house and when and he arose
and departed to his house but when the
multitude saw it they marveled and
glorified God which had given such power
unto men this same Jesus
is the judge in your case the same Jesus
that forgave sin the same Jesus that
healed the same Jesus that brought back
to life this same Jesus is the judge in
your case and now I need you to know
something beloved here is some super
good news according to Hebrews chapter
13 verse 8 the Bible says this Jesus
Christ the same
the
same the
same
yesterday and
today and
forever come on
y'all listen
y'all Jesus Christ doesn't
change so the same Jesus
that that showed compassion and mercy
and love to humanity when he was here on
Earth that same Jesus is the judge in
your
case now Jesus doesn't
change he's the same Jesus that same
Jesus beloved is judging us that same
Jesus beloved is the judge in our
case that it's the same Jesus that said
this notice with me Matthew
19:13 then were there brought unto him
little children that he should put his
hands on them and pray and the
disciples rebuked them but Jesus said
suffer little children and forbid them
not to come unto me for such is the
Kingdom of Heaven listen to me y'all
this same
Jesus this same Jesus listen that
that loved
children that same Jesus is the
judge in our
case come on y'all put put a one in the
chat if you are getting a little bit
more happier than when this sermon began
that same Jesus is the judge in our case
that same Jesus is the one who is going
to determine whether we live with him
forever in heaven or
not that
man come back with me again to the
screen John chapter 8 John chapter 8:2
the Bible says this and early in the
morning he came again into the temple
and all the people came unto him and he
sat down and taught them and the scribes
and Pharisees brought unto him a woman
taken in adultery and when they had set
her in the midst they say unto him
Master this woman was taken in adultery
in in the very
act now Moses in the law commanded us
that such should be stoned but what
sayest thou this they said tempting him
but Jesus stooped down with his finger
wrote on the ground as though he had not
heard them so when they continued asking
him he lifted himself up and said unto
them he that is without sin among you
let him cast the first first
stone again he stooped down and wrote on
the ground and when they heard it being
convicted by their own conscience went
out one by one and beginning beginning
at the eldest even unto the last and
Jesus was left alone and the woman
standing in the midst when Jesus had
lifted himself up he saw none but the
woman and said unto Heroman where are
those thine accuser he has no man
condemned thee she said no man Lord and
Jesus said neither do I condemn thee go
and sin no more now pause for a second
y'all put in the chat for me
this
same
Jesus just put that in the chat for me
for a moment
please this same
Jesus who resided over a case where a
woman is clearly guilty and caught in
the act of adultery this same
Jesus that said to the woman go and sin
no
more this same Jesus is the judge in our
case now how many of you how many of you
beginning to feel a little hope in your
heart in a way different than you have
felt
before this same Jesus now we got to
under we got to break this down so I can
help you to understand what I'm saying
and what I'm not saying so so check this
out where did they bring this
woman where did they bring this
woman where was Jesus
preaching come on y'all where was he
preaching he was preaching in the temple
so they brought this woman to the temple
come on y'all let's go let let's go come
with me to Exodus 25 verse eight the
where the Bible says God instructed the
children of Israel let them make me a
sanctuary that I may dwell among them
and verse 10 they shall make uh an ark
of shittin wood two cubits and a half
and uh shall be the length thereof and a
cubit and a half the breadth thereof and
a cubit and a half the height thereof
and thou shalt put into the ark the
testimony which I shall give thee so we
know that inside the Ark of the co
inside the the the the
sanctuary was the Ark of the Covenant
that had the law of God yeah the law of
God which is The Ten Commandments
written on tables of stone that is the
law that that God instructed Moses to
put into the ark and so when they bring
this woman CAU adultery she has broken
this law that says Thou shalt not commit
adultery she is guilty as
whatever but beloved I need y'all to
understand
something because the ark had
another there was something else added
to the
ark there was something else that was a
part of the
Ark y'all are saying Mercy Mercy yeah
that's a that's an appropriate word
because if we go to the same chapter
Exodus 25:1 17 the text goes on to say
and thou shalt make a mercy seat of pure
gold two cubits and a half shall be the
length thereof and two cubits and a half
shall be the height thereof watch this
and thou shalt make two cherubin of gold
of beaten work shalt thou make them in
the two two ends of the mercy seat and
make one cherub on the one end and the
other cherub on the other end of The
Mercy Seat even of The Mercy Seat shall
you make the cherubims on the two ends
thereof and the cherubim shall stretch
forth their wings on
high
covering the mercy seat with their wings
and their faces shall look one to
another toward the mercy she seat shall
the faces of the cherubim be now now
let's break this down y'all let's break
this down
see God is when God tells Moses to make
this Mercy Seat he says put it above the
law put it above the
law now now why are we putting it above
the law it's above the law to cover
it so there's a covering
over there is a covering over the law
and it's called The Mercy
Seat and then you got these two angels
that spread their wings and cover the
mercy seat and their faces their faces
are looking to The Mercy Seat so if you
walk into a crowd of people and you see
everybody looking somewhere right what
are you g to do you're naturally going
to look to the place that they're
looking yeah and if you see two Divine
beings who are standing in the very same
in the very presence of God and they're
both looking at something now watch this
y'all they're not looking at
God they're not looking at the
law their faces are
towards The Mercy
Seat could it be that that what God is
trying to do is to get our attention
on The Mercy
Seat do y'all realize something come
come with me to the screen let let Psalm
51 sink in in a different way to you
right now have mercy upon me oh God have
mercy upon me oh God according to thy
loving kindness according to the
multitude of thy Tender Mercies blot out
my transgression Wash Me thoroughly from
my iniquity and cleanse me from my sin
for I acknowledge my transgression and
my sin is ever before me against thee
have I sinned and against thee only and
done this evil in thy sight that thou
mightest be justified when thou speak
and cleared when thou judgest David is
saying listen Lord do not judge me by
the
law because if you do I am done I am
lost I have already sinned and that is
why I am confessing it to you I'm
agreeing with you that I have broken the
law I'm agreeing with you that I was
wrong in doing so and now the only thing
I can I can depend upon I cannot point
to the law in judgment and say look I've
kept it the only thing I can point
to I don't care if you have been a
Seventh Day Adventist since birth I
don't care if you are fourth generation
ad Adventist beloved you will not be
able to point to the law in the Judgment
because if you do so you are already
condemned and so while we acknowledge
the law of God and acknowledge that the
law is good and just and holy we have to
throw ourselves on the come on y'all on
the what on the what on the mercy of God
why because once I broke the law once I
am already it's already done
y'all we have every right to be lost
none of us can point to the law and say
lord judge me according to the law
because then
H now watch this y'all watch this watch
watch this that same Jesus watch this
come with me to the screen watch this
y'all hatred stirreth up stries but love
coverthe
Jo why are the
Angels spreading their wings Over The
Mercy
Seat could it be that God is trying to
demonstrate that it is his love that
covers our faults our transgressions our
sins
for wait a minute
y'all that same
Jesus who is defined as love the Bible
says hatred Stir of strife but love
covers all you realize that what Jesus
is trying to do he's trying to do
everything to cover our
sins come again notice with me on the
screen Proverbs 17:9 he that cover a
transgression seeketh love but he that
repeat the matter separateth very
friends wait a
minute so you mean that it is God's it
is Jesus's love that leads him to cover
trans
ression that's what he's trying to do
that's what the mercy seat is all about
listen come to me repent of your sins
and I got you covered you ever hear
someone say that I got you covered hey
I'm trying to get into this place hey I
got you covered man don't worry about it
I got you covered Jesus is tell is
telling us if you would but trust me
I've got you
covered listen to this proverbs 11:13
taale Bearer reveal the secrets but he
that is of a faithful Spirit conceal the
matter beloved Jesus is of a faithful
spirit and that same Jesus who is of a
faithful spirit is the same Jesus who is
presiding over your case as the
judge and now we can begin to understand
Psalm
91:4 he shall cover thee with his
feathers and under his wings shalt thou
trust his truth shall be thy shield and
thy buckler you understand Jesus beloved
is trying to cover
us he's saying I got you covered in the
Judgment if you will but let
me and he's trying to tell us
beloved that the thing we have to throw
ourselves on is his
Mercy listen again 1 Peter chapter 4 4:8
Above All Above and above all things
have fervent charity among yourselves
for charity shall cover the multitude of
sins yes yes yes but now watch this he
that
coverthe but whosoever confesseth and
forsaketh them shall have what Mercy
listen y'all the covering of the mercy
seat and the angels covering The Mercy
Seat is not designed to teach us to
cover our sins if we try to cover our
sins it means we're
guilty Jesus says I need you to bring
your sins to me and I will cover them I
will cover
you how y'all doing I need you to
understand right no one in the Judgment
can point to the law if you have a
choice you're standing before God you're
in the judgment and God says how would
you like to be judged the law or Mercy
what are you pointing to put it in the
chat for me please what are you pointing
to in this judgment what are you hoping
that God is going to extend to you in
this judgment now if you're good and
you've done everything right you don't
need
Mercy I need you to understand Mercy is
not for those who already got it they
already got it down why do I need Mercy
if I haven't done anything wrong Mercy
is not for the
perfect please please I need to see in
the chat how many of you are going to
ask
God for
Mercy you see Beloved the
investigative judgment is really about
the
mercy I don't know if y'all caught
that in the investigative Jud judgement
we tend to focus so much on the Judgment
that we fail to understand that the real
essence of the judgment is his
Mercy watch this y'all watch this come
with me to the screen Romans 3:19 now we
know that whatsoever things the law
saith it says to them that are under the
law that every mouth may be stopped and
the whole world become guilty before God
please listen to
me no one not a single individual will
be able to
say
uh well according to the law you need to
let me into
heaven because all have sinned the Bible
says the whole world will be no one will
be able to argue based on the law of why
they should be in
heaven
because the law demands Perfection and
even if you kept the law perfect from a
certain point on till the end of your
life it still wouldn't matter because
once you have sinned you are guilty of
breaking the
law I will never sin again from this day
forward that's not getting you into
heaven you're you're just ceasing to sin
until you die is not the KE that get you
into heaven beloved listen to me once
you have sinned it is Mercy and mercy
only but the good news is this same
Jesus that's the good news y'all this
same
Jesus
listen follow me follow me watch this
Psalm 19:12 who who can understand his
errors cleanse thou me from Secret
faults listen y'all you know what secret
Faults
Are secret Faults Are The Faults that I
don't even understand I was doing
myself The Faults I don't even
understand I was
doing
myself listen to
this uh Albert Barnes says of this in
the Albert Barnes comment tell you
speaking on this verse who can
understand his errors the word rendered
errors is derived from a verb which
means to wander to go astray then to do
wrong to transgress it refers to the
wandering or departures from the law of
God and the question seems to have been
asked in view of the Purity the
strictness and the extent of the law of
God in view of a law so pure so holy so
strict in its
demands and so extended in its
requirements asserting jurisdiction over
the thought thoughts the words and the
whole life who can recall the number of
times that he has thus departed from
such a law the language is such as every
man who has had who has any just sense
of the nature and the requirements of
the law and the just view of his own
life must use in reference to himself
the reason why any man is elated with a
conviction of his own goodness is that
he has no just sense of the requirements
of the law of God and the more anyone
studies the law the more he will be
convinced of the extent of his own
depravity the more you understand
Beloved the Holiness of the law of God
the more you understand just how far you
fall from
it
James chapter 2 says this for whosoever
shall keep the whole law and yet offend
in one point he is guilty of all for he
that said do not commit adultery also
said do not kill now thou commit no
adultery yet if thou kill Thou Art
become a transgressor of the law so
speak he and so do is they that shall be
judged by the law of Liberty for he
shall have judgment without Mercy that
has showed no mercy and mercy rejoices
against judgment now this is heavy you
guys this is
heavy James is writing here he says
listen I need you to speak and do as
they that shall be judged by the law of
Liberty now what is the doing that he's
talking about what is the doing here is
the doing for he shall have judgment
without Mercy that has showed no mercy
now let me ask you a question y'all
let's come back back for a
moment you have an option of judgment
with Mercy or judgment without Mercy now
why in the world would we first of all
which one would you want judgment with
Mercy or judgment without Mercy which
one put it in the chat for me please
judgment with Mercy or judgment without
Mercy I I don't need Mercy I can depend
on how I have kept the law I keep the
Sabbath you know I believe in ten
commandments so let's just go ahead and
go with law that's all I need God how
many of you are ready to do
that what nobody that's right not one
not one we want judgment with Mercy now
why do we need Mercy Mercy is for that
which has not been done correctly Mercy
is for that which requires Grace which
means there is Fault in
it
so so so the Bible here is telling
us the only way you're saved is through
Mercy however if you do not extend Mercy
to others you will have no mercy
extended to
you
uhoh
uhoh do y'all see
this Mercy
in order to receive Mercy look at the
Look What the Lord did the same judge
did in this case with the woman caught
in
adultery he extended
mercy so
now Lord what you're telling
me is that if I really want to be like
you you mean I've got to extend Mercy
like
you
did you see that last verse where it
says Mercy rejoices against
judgment that word to Rejoice against
against it means to exalt against that
is over to boast to glory to Rejoice
against in other words Mercy is
preferred over
judgment that's what the text is
saying Mercy is per referred over
judgment beloved in the investigative
judgment we are to depend upon the mercy
of God because if God gives us judgment
and Justice we're all
lost come back with me to the screen
Matthew 1821 then came Peter to to him
saying Lord how often shall my brother
sin against me and I forgive him till
seven times Jesus said unto him I say
not unto thee until seven times but
until 70 times seven therefore is the
Kingdom of Heaven liken unto a certain
King which would take account of his
servants and when he had begun to reckon
one was brought unto him which owed him
10,000 talents now I need y'all to pause
for a second here I need y'all to pause
for a second here because in this
Parable in this
Parable the servant the guy that owes
the King money is a servant meaning he
serves
him in this Parable an account of
judgment an account is being taken of
his servants it's a
judgment and he's not judging those who
don't claim to be his servants he's
judging those who are his
servants and here it is the servant owes
him
money which means the servant wasn't
doing everything
correctly let's read
on but as far as far as much as he had
not to pay his Lord commanded him to be
so oh no no no no let's go back let's go
back we got to go back let's go
back okay here we go um when he had
begun to reckon one was brought unto him
which owed him 10,000 talents but for as
much as he had not to pay his Lord
commanded him to be sold and his wife
and
children and all that he had and payment
to be made the servant therefore fell
down and worshiped him saying Lord have
patience with me and I will pay the all
then the lord of the servant was moved
with compassion and loed him and forgave
him the debt in other words he said you
don't need to pay
me come here y'all listen to me he said
you don't need to pay me I forgive
you do y'all understand
do y'all understand that in the Judgment
there is nothing we can do to pay God
what we owe
him come on come back and I I need you
to catch this I need you to to follow
this carefully in the
Judgment in the
Judgment we are already owing God what
we cannot
pay and what God does is he's saying I'm
going to be merciful to
you I'm going to be merciful to
you the parable goes on to say this
verse verse verse 28 but the same
servant went out and found one of his
fellow servants which owed him 100 tense
and he laid hands on him and took him by
the throat saying pay me what you owe me
and his fellow servant fell down to his
feet and besought him saying have
patience with me and I will pay thee all
and he would not but went and cast him
into prison till he should pay the debt
so when the the fellow servants saw what
was done they were very sorry and came
and told unto their lord all that was
done then his Lord after he had called
him said unto him oh thy Wicked servant
I forgave thee all that debt because
thou desired me should not thou have had
compassion on thy fellow servant even as
I had pity on thee and his Lord was
wroth and delivered him to the
tormentors till he should pay all that
was due to him so likewise shall my
heavenly father do unto you if you from
your hearts do not keep the
Commandments oh if you from your hearts
do not forgive everyone his brother
their trespasses listen to me you
guys it was
Mercy that was extended to the
servants yes the servants are to keep
the Commandments yes the servants are to
abide by the law but you need to
understand that God is not judging us
based on that per se because if he were
to actually judge us based on the law
everybody is
lost so we are literally throwing
ourselves on The Mercy Seat of
God Lord have mercy see on
me see now we can understand Micah 7:18
who is a god like unto thee that
paronthi and passeth by the
transgression of the remnant of his
Heritage he retaineth not his anger
forever because he Delights in mer in
Mercy he Delights in Mercy he will turn
again he will have compassion on us he
will subdue our iniquities and thou will
cast all their sins in to the depths of
the sea wow
y'all
wow how many of you are really liking
that mercy seat right
now how many of y'all listen y'all there
is something I'm about to share with you
remember we were talking about that
moment for a moment I haven't even
gotten there yet I'm just trying to
build and and show you beloved
that some times we can inadvertently
depend upon something in the Judgment
that we will in no way pass and it
brings a condemnation a a continual
struggling in our own minds of
condemnation if you know the
judge if you know the judge and how he
operates you begin to see something
beautiful about the Jud judgment
yall listen to this in Exodus 3318 God
speaking to Moses says I beseech thee
Moses saying to God I beseech thee show
me my show me thy glory and he said I
will make all my goodness pass before
thee and I will proclaim the name of the
Lord before thee and will be gracious to
whom I will be gracious and will show
Mercy unto whom I will show Mercy it's
almost like he's saying listen I reserve
the right listen to me
y'all
it's as if God is saying Jesus is saying
I reserve the right to show Mercy to
whoever I choose to show Mercy
to she broke the law she deserves to to
die Jesus says I reserve the right to
show
Mercy I reserve the right
to show Mercy over
judgment now I don't know about yall but
listen who of us wants to go into a
courtroom and not receive the mercy of
the judge
especially if we're
guilty I need y'all to see this listen
to this Matthew 5:43 you have heard that
it is said has been told love thy
neighbor and hate thine enemy but I say
unto you love your enemies bless them
that curse you do good to them that hate
you and pray for them which despitefully
use you and persecute you that you may
be the children of your father which is
in heaven for he maketh his son to rise
on the evil and on the good and sendeth
reain on the just and on the unjust for
if you love them which love you what
reward do you have do not even the
publicans the same and if you salute
your brethren only what do you more than
others do not even the publicans the
same not watch this be ye therefore
perfect even as your father which is in
heaven is perfect wait a minute
what what is
perfection Perfection is showing Mercy
to
others because that's what Jesus
did
wow wow wow wow wow come on keep moving
let's keep moving we we're getting
somewhere I need you to follow this
beloved let us love one another for love
is of
God and everyone that loveth is born of
God and knoweth God he that loveth not
knoweth not God for God is what
love in this was manifested the love of
God toward us because that God sent his
son because God sent his son his only
begot godten son into the world that we
might live through him hearing his love
not that we love God but that he loved
us and sent his son to be the
propitiation for our sins I'm GNA keep
reading and I need to get a drink of
water
beloved if
God so loved us we ought to love one
another no man has seen God at any time
if we love one another
God dwelleth in us and his love is
perfected in US hereby we know that we
dwell in him and he in us because he has
given us his
Spirit oh forgive me
y'all
okay God says the way that you know that
I'm dwelling in
you is if you love one
another is if you're merciful to one
another
is if you're forgiving to one
another if you are forbearing with one
another God Jesus is the definition of
love and watch this this same
Jesus this same Jesus who is love notice
how the Bible describes love in 1
Corinthians 13:4 charity suffereth long
and is kind envieth not
charity vaunteth not itself is not
puffed up does not behave unseemingly
seeketh not her own is not easily
provoked thinketh no evil rejoices not
in
iniquity but rejoices in truth beareth
all things believeth all things hopeth
all things endureth all
things this is powerful y'all the Bible
says hearing is our love made perfect
that we may have boldness in the day of
judgment get that up on the screen watch
this hearing is our love made perfect
that we may have boldness in the day of
judgment because as he is so are we in
the
world there is no fear in love but
perfect love cast out fear because fear
has torment it is not made perfect in
love we love him because he first loved
us and now watch the very next Words If
any man say I love God and hates his
brother he is a liar for he that loveth
not his brother whom he has seen how can
he love God whom he has not seen do
y'all see
this this same Jesus is telling
us that the standard of the
Judgment yes it is his law but above
that it is his mercy and if we exercise
Mercy if we are Lov and forgiving to
others we can expect this same Jesus to
be merciful and forgiving to
us not guess not
suppose
expect we can have that boldness in the
day of judgment why because we're
depending upon the mercy of
God we're not taking for granted his law
we're not taking for granted his Justice
we understand it and that's why we plead
for his
mercy and it's this same
Jesus this same Jesus Remember in Luke
23:42 remember that thief on the
cross that said Lord remember me when
you come into your
kingdom
y the man said said remember me when you
come into your kingdom and Jesus reads
that as please forgive
me can y'all can
y'all the same Jesus come back to the
screen the same
Jesus that was looking for an
opportunity to save this thief on the CR
what remember you I'm interpreting that
as forgive me okay I got you
covered I got you
covered here is a
man that
seems desperate to save that's the judge
y'all that's the judge in your
case
watch this and he showed me Joshua the
high
priest standing before the angel of the
Lord and Satan standing at his right
hand to resist him and the Lord said
unto Satan the Lord rebuke thee Oh Satan
even the Lord that has chosen Jerusalem
rebuked thee is not this a brand plucked
out of the
fire now Joshua was clothed with filthy
garments and stood before the angel okay
hold on y'all
this Joshua the high
priest is standing in filthy garments
before the
Lord he's not standing in good garments
he's not standing in clean garments he's
standing in filthy garments before the
Lord what's Satan is saying about him is
obviously
true but here he is standing before the
Lord and what does the Lord
do just like he does with the woman
caught in
adultery come on you
guys this same
Jesus
that's the judge in your
case I got something mindblowing to show
you y'all
come come on we're getting ready to
we're getting ready to to to pull this
thing to a close I need you to see
this
so let's just
go let's go
here Hebrews chapter 3:15 while is said
today if you will hear his voice Harden
not your your hearts as in the
provocation for some when they had heard
did provoke how be it not all that came
out of Egypt by Moses but with whom was
he grieved 40
years was it not them that had sinned
whose carcasses fell in the
wilderness and to whom swear he that
they should not enter into the rest but
to them that believe not so we see they
could not enter in because of
what put it in the chat y'all because of
what why could they not enter
in come back with me for a
moment they couldn't enter
in because of
unbelief oh
wow okay so they could not enter into
the promised
land because of of
unbelief and because they sinned and as
a result of their unbelief and their sin
what happened to their
bodies the Bible says they died in the
wilderness are these people GNA be in
heaven yes or
no put it in the chat for me please are
these people going to be in heaven yes
or no
and I'm going to wait for the answer
here so I'm waiting to see your
responses are these people going to be
in heaven yes or
no so they entered not into the promised
land because of
unbelief they entered in they did not
enter into the promised land um because
they sinned and the evidence was they
died in the
wilderness
all right
so check this out
y'all check this out let's go back to
the screen let's go back to the screen
so the Bible says here in numbers 14:17
this is God speaking to Mo this is Moses
speaking to God now I beseech thee so
the children of Israel have just sinned
against
God the Bible says here now I beseech
thee let the
power let the power of my Lord be great
according as thou Hast spoken saying the
Lord is
longsuffering and of great
Mercy forgiving iniquity and
transgressions and by no means clearing
the guilty visiting the iniquity of the
fathers upon the children unto the third
and fourth generation pardon I beseech
Thee the iniquity of this people
according unto to the greatness of thy
mercy and as thou Hast forgiven this
people from Egypt even until
now and the Lord said I have pardoned
according to Thy word stop for a second
y'all just just come back come back with
me come back let me ask you a
question no no no no no no we need to go
back we need to go back check this out
y'all let's go back to the screen I Need
You and I hope y'all are sitting
down the Lord said I have pardoned
according to Thy word but as truly as I
live all the Earth shall be filled with
the glory of the
Lord because all those men which have
seen my glory and my Miracles which I
did in Egypt and in the wilderness and
have tempted me now these 10 times and
have not hearkened to my
voice surely they shall not enter
into
heaven surely they shall not enter into
heaven
Surly they shall not
enter is that what the text says
the text says surely they shall not see
the land which I swear unto their
fathers neither shall any of them that
provoked me see
it so hold on a second come back for a
moment did God forgive them yes or no
put it in the chat please did God
forgive them did God did Moses intercede
for them and did God say okay I have
pardoned
them y'all listen to me Canaan is not
heaven the land of
Israel was not
heaven so so what God is doing here is
he's put listen listen the he's forgiven
them but their punishment was you can't
go into the promised
land so in actuality
beloved yes there will be people who
died in the wilderness who don't go to
heaven and yes there may be some people
who died in the wilderness who were
punished because of that
act that will actually be in
heaven and you want to know how I can
say that
definitively let me show you how yeah
I'm setting y'all up come back with me
to the screen y'all Numbers Chapter 20
this is six chapters later watch this
y'all we're talking about a God who is
doing whatever he can to save as many as
he can numbers 20:10 and Moses and Aaron
gathered the congregation together
before the Rock and he said unto them he
now ye Rebels must must we fetch you
water out of this rock that's Moses
talking in anger and Moses lifted up his
Rod his hand and with his Rod he smot
The Rock twice and the water came out
abundantly and the congregation drank
and the Beast also all right now watch
this and the Lord said unto Moos spake
unto Moses and Aaron next verse because
you believed me
not pause for a second pause for a
second come back to the
come back with me in Hebrews 3 we read
with whom was the Lord
grieved those that what did not believe
one therefore their bodies what fell in
the car in the wilderness they did not
enter the promised
land come back to the
screen and the Lord spake unto Moses and
Aaron saying because you believe me not
Moses to sanctify me in the eyes of the
children of Israel therefore you shall
not bring the congregation into the land
which I have given them this is the
water of merbah because the children of
Israel strove with the Lord and he was
Sanctified in them I need y'all to catch
this beloved
Moses
carcass fell in the
wilderness in fact in fact watch this in
Deuteronomy 3 listen to what Moses says
and I besought the Lord at that time
saying Lord God thou has begun to show
thy servant thy greatness and thy Mighty
hand for what God is there in heaven or
in Earth that can do according to thy
works and according to thy might I pray
thee God let me go over and see the good
land that is beyond Jordan that goodly
mountain and Lebanon but the
Lord but the Lord was wro wroth with me
for your sakes and would not hear me and
the Lord said unto me Let It suffice
thus speak no more unto me of this
matter get thee up into the top of Mount
pisga of top of pisga and lift up thine
eyes Westward and northward and
Southward and Eastward and behold it
with th eyes for Thou shalt not go over
this Jordan but charge Joshua and
encourage him and strengthen him for he
shall go over before this people and he
shall cause them to inherit the land
which Thou shalt
see are y'all catching
this Moses is one of the people being
being talked about in Hebrews 3 who did
not enter into the promised land because
of unbelief because of his sin and
yet the same Moses whose body whose
carcass fell in the
wilderness that same Moses come on y'all
that s come to the screen that same
Moses and six days after Jesus taketh
Peter watch this six days Jesus Take
Peter James John and his brother and
bringing them up into a high mountain
apart and was transfigured before them
and his face did shine as the sun and
his reignment was as white as the light
and behold there appeared unto
them come on y'all come on
y'all there appeared unto them Moses
hold on wait a
second did we not just read that God was
wroth with
Moses did we not just read in Hebrews 3
that those they did not enter into the
promis land of Canaan because of their
unbelief what is Moses come back with me
y'all come back with me to the screen
what is Moses doing in
heaven and if Moses is in heaven as a
token is it possible that there were
some people back then I don't know I
can't give you a number but is it
possible that there are people back then
that died in the wilderness facing the
Judgment of God but they were not
necessarily cut off from the kingdom of
heaven to come I need y'all to
understand something
y'all God is doing everything in his
power to save
us yes he punishes and yes he he
chastens and he chastened Moses but
beloved Moses died was resurrected and
taken to he Moses speak no more to me
about this Moses doesn't know what's
coming Moses just like okay well I guess
that's it I guess I'm done Moses Pro
Moses probably dies thinking am I in the
good graces of God or
not
y' can y'all understand can y'all see
just how this same
Jesus this same Jes Jesus is our
judge listen to me I'm not saying that
people back then who who sinned and
never repented go that that's not what
I'm
saying everything is about
Mercy everything is about
repentance so if there were people back
then who repented even though they did
not enter a he a an
Earthly piece of land if they repented
and even though they die they die in the
wilderness there guess what just as
Moses is in heaven now they will be in
heaven in the
resurrection do you see this y'all Jesus
is trying Jesus is holding out hope for
us until the very day that we die and so
when we think about the judgment and
we're fearful all I need you to
understand beloved is I know the
judge I know the
judge I know his character I know what
he's
like we're almost done the Bible says
the Bible says here H H uh check this
out y'all um
um lord lord lord Lord take this out the
Bible speaks of this story in the Old
Testament very quick story Hebrews 9:22
and ham the father of Canaan saw the
nakedness of his father and told his two
Brethren without and Shem and took a
garment and laid it upon both their
shoulders and went backward and covered
the nakedness of their father and their
faces were backward and they saw not the
nakedness of their father beloved listen
to me do you know that this is a picture
of Jesus and what Jesus does for us
beloved when we are in our nakedness and
our shame Jesus isn't trying to expose
us he's trying to cover us he's Desiring
to save us and beloved that same thing
that Shem and did is what we ought
to be doing to we ought to be covering
others father forgive them Lord cover
them with your righteousness Lord H uh
help me to cover that person to forgive
that person we ought to be covering just
as the angels in the at that Mercy Seat
are showing the mercy of God they're
covering The Mercy Seat beloved because
we are covered by God we should be
covering
others y'all catch this because we are
covered by God we should be covering
others
people who sin against us I got you
covered I got you covered how can you be
so nice because look man Jesus did it
for me Jesus did it for
me
Jesus did it for
me and so the Bible
says when the son of
man shall
come
let me get this slide to where it
is all right when the son of man shall
come in his glory and all the Holy
Angels with him then shall he sit upon
the throne of his glory and before him
shall be gathered all nations and they
shall separate them one from another as
a Shepherd divideth his sheep from the
goats and he shall set the Sheep on the
right hand but the goats on the left
y'all catch this are y'all getting
this then shall the king say unto them
on his right hand Come Ye blessed of my
father inherit the Kingdom prepared for
you from the foundation of the world for
I was a hunger and you gave me meat I
was thirsty you gave me drink I was a
stranger and you took me in naked and
you clothed me I was sick and you
visited me I was in prison and you came
unto me then shall the righteous answer
him saying Lord when we did we see you
hungry and fed thee or thirsty and gave
thee drink when saw we thee a stranger
and took thee in or naked and clothed
thee or when saw we sick and in prison
and came unto thee and the King shall
answer and say unto them verily I say
unto you in as much as you've done it
unto the least of these my brethren you
have done it unto me you have done it
unto me come on Y come back I got one
more verse for you and then we're gonna
close this
out um you see the basis of the
Judgment how did you treat other
people is this downplaying the law nope
because the law is summarized by loving
God and loving your
neighbor and because so often we
approach the law from a very what is
written aspect we miss the greater per
we miss that aspect of
Mercy that the Lord
demands it's not just the ark it's the
ark and The Mercy
Seat and when I realize that no matter
how well I keep the law from this point
forward if I stand before God and he
marks every sin that I have ever done
the ones I forgot to confess listen
y'all it's a done deal and all that you
have is a fearful looking forward to of
judgment but if you know the
judge come on
y'all if you go into a court and you
know that the judge is your
cousin officer gave you the you you know
the judge is no body else knows the
judge your you know the judge is your
cousin you're going in
like beloved if you realize that the
judge is your nearest of
kin there's no need to be
afraid and now you realize the reason I
love the Lord is because listen to me
y'all listen here here's our closing
verse here's our closing verse I need
y'all to to understand understand the
significance of this after this I beheld
and low a great multitude which no man
could number of all Nations and kindreds
and peoples and tongues stood Before the
Throne and before the lamb clothed with
white robes and Palms in their hands and
cried with a loud voice saying salvation
to our god which sth upon the throne and
unto the lamb do y'all understand the
significance of this
text come back with me come back to the
screen how in the world how in the world
is it
possible that in heaven there will be a
great multitude that you cannot even
number how is that
possible come on y'all think through
this with
me the the standard that we think of in
heaven right is
like who who shall then be
saved are you telling
me that there's a great multitude that
is so multitud is that people can't even
number it of
people who are like yes we got this all
under
control
nah
nope if there's a great multitude in
heaven that no man could
number that can only be by the mercy of
God
y'all that can only be by the mercy of
God none of them are going to be like
hey you know why I'm
here because of God's justice I did you
need need mercy no I didn't me mercy I
was
good every one of them are in heaven
because of the mercy seat sitting on top
of the
Ark there will be some people there who
did not understand all the contents of
the Ark who didn't understand that they
needed to keep the Sabbath who didn't
understand about the law of God but
because they exercise the mercy of God
God's like I got you covered there are
some people who who there are people who
will not be there who knew the law of
God knew that it had to be kept and
strive to keep it but refused to show
mercy and therefore were judged strictly
by judgment by Justice and
therefore but where are they at not
here beloved you got to know the judge
and when you know the judge I remember
back in the day you know if you're you
know when you are a partyer and you go
into the club and then you be the guy
the guy there who who who knows you or
knows your friend and he sees y' it's
like I got y'all come on I got y'all
cover I got y'all
covered I I know it's a crude
illustration a club or whatever but
listen
y'all when you realize that you know the
judge I'm telling you it it changes
everything the
pressure of you saying what you know
how what can I do to convince the judge
to let me into
heaven
no no no no
no I'm going to strive to keep the law
of God I'm going to strive to keep the
Commandments of God and the testimony of
Jesus but I know that it is his mercy
and beloved that means that the only
people that are lost are those that
refused to show Mercy to others those
that either refuse to acknowledge the
law or refuse to show Mercy to
others I I don't need a law in my life I
don't need God's law I don't I want to
do wrong or those who said yeah you know
I can be like God but I'm not showing
Mercy this morning I got
up and
uh I had a message on
Instagram here's the message let's go
look on the screen here's the message it
was from my best friend
here's what the message said hello Ivor
how's it going and then my automatic
contact responded so I didn't see it
this was 4:51 a.m. in the morning and
then it said again good morning brother
about 7:51
a.m. s responded hey T how are you he
said everything is smooth here man I'm
feeling upbeat every here here
everything is proceeding smoothly I'm
feeling upbeat and full of Hope for the
upcoming year what have you been
experimenting with
lately so I said oh nothing much just
doing life as usual how about you now
now let come back with me for a moment
come back to the screen for a
moment can you see me all
right the moment that I saw hello Ivor
how are you doing and it was 4:51 a.m. I
started laughing like this this this
morning so the message was sent at 451
but I saw it this morning at like 7 8
o'clock and when I saw it I I just
started laughing and laughing and and
laughing and I was like I gotta
respond because first of all te is TE is
not going to be up at 4:51 a.m. in the
morning that's number one number two
hello Ivor how are
you we don't talk like
that so I
I was just like I gotta screenshot this
and I gotta I gotta send this to T and
tell him about the conversation I'm
having with him right
now it was hilarious y'all that I had to
engage in a conversation so what are you
up to oh I'm not doing anything you know
how's your life been and I was like
where's this going and ultimately here's
where it was going check this out I'm g
go back to the screen so I said uh oh oh
nothing much just doing life as usual
how about you and then he says I hope
your I hope you succeed all through
brother for me I've been focusing my
resources on creating new and passive
income streams I started dabbling in
rentals and digital assets which have
been lucrative I even hopped onto onto
crypto train haha have you got anything
going on there and I'm like what how can
I get into this so after this I don't
know if it was a bot or what but after
this discussion I just screenshotted it
and I sent it to my best
friend come back to the screen I sent it
to my I was like T
check this out here and his response was
yo as soon as whoever this is said hello
ior how are you that was a dead giveaway
and he gave a smile he gave a laughing
face and I was like T you know what I'm
gonna use this in my
sermon I'm G use this in my
sermon I knew immediately from the from
the tone of the text from the I knew
that's
Nazi somebody's you know jacked his
account or whatever but that's not
him and I was thinking you know what
that's how the devil tries to do us with
Jesus but if we know Jesus if we
know our friend our best
friend we will have no reason to be
afraid how many of you looking forward
to looking forward to your
judge put that one in the chat if you
are excited that your judge is
Jesus may you never look at the Judgment
the
same may you
understand
that your salvation
is dependent upon the one who has
redeemed
you every one of us that will be in
heaven are there because of the mercy of
God because of the mercy of the judge
and that is
it and when you know that you can throw
yourself at the mercy of this
judge having done everything you
possibly can
out of love for
him if you love me keep my Commandments
if you love me I need you to demonstrate
Mercy those two
things and I know that you're
commandment keeping I know there are
things you you're doing that you don't
even realize or say there are things
that there are things you have forgotten
to repent there are things you never
thought to repent of listen you are but
human if you will allow if you will
trust me with
everything I'm going to Grant you my
Mercy
what what a powerful thought
y'all what a powerful
thought May the mercy of God become a
new living reality to you this same
Jesus this same
Jesus that's the one that
sits as your
judge
remember that
y'all remember
that Heavenly
Father Lord we thank you for sending
your
son we thank you that you sent him so
that we could see the character of the
judge who was going to judge
us Lord you have shown us throughout
scriptures that you are not willing that
any should perish but that all should
come to
repentance and you've even showed us
Lord that we need to be careful about
how we judge how is Samson in the in
Hebrews 11 as part of the Hall of Faith
Samson he's the one that had his eyes
put out because of his own
sin and yet there he is in the Hall of
Faith David Abraham Mo these men who had
errors in their lives
Lord we have seen
today that you are desperate to save us
and that you reserve the right to show
mercy and that you will do that for
everyone who will throw themselves upon
your mercy but Lord remind us that if we
expect Mercy from you we must
demonstrate and and and show
consistently Mercy to
others
remind us Lord that the basis of your of
your judgment is your
law Mercy does not cancel judgment
judgment does not cancel Mercy but they
both meet and kiss together in you Lord
and so father we are pleading and
praying we throw ourselves at the feet
of the throne of grace the Throne of
Mercy please Lord forgive us of our sins
and may our hearts
rest
assured in this that we know the judge
and that he will indeed be merciful to
us in Jesus name we pray amen and amen I
want to invite you all to the uh alter
live discussion after uh uh that is that
will take place now we're going to put
that link in the chat um and um please
feel free to to to to jump on to discuss
what have uh learned from either Sabbath
school or this message which I I hope is
a lifechanging message um and again may
God bless you and may God change your
walk may may may your approach to Jesus
be one that is not based on fear but one
that is based on love admiration
and and
peace love admiration and peace so may
God bless you and uh we'll see you over
on alter live um have a good rest of
your day
amen